Guide to the Rutherfurd Collection 1642-1845 MS 531
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Correspondence and Documents, 1642-1845 (bulk 1734-1796)
  - Subseries I.D: Volume III, 1742-1766
    - [85] Letter from William Alexander to Abram Dow, 1756 January 4
    - [87] Orders from P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 January 14
    - [87] Orders and Instructions from General William Shirley to P.V.B. Livingston, &c., 1756 January 5
    - [89] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 February 7
    - [91] Copy of letter from John Murray to William Alexander, 1756 February 7
    - [93] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 February 11
    - [93] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 March 1
    - [95] James Stevenson enclosed, 1756 March 13
    - [95] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 March 13
    - [95] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 March 28
    - [97] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 March 15
    - [99] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 February 23
    - [101] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 March 22
    - [102] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 March 23
    - [102] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 March 27
    - [103] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 April 5
    - [105] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 8
    - [105] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 6
    - [107] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 15
    - [107] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 16
    - [109] Copy of warrant from General Shirley for P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 16
    - [111] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 17
    - [111] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 19
    - [113] A Criticism upon the course of the English Ministry and conduct of the war, supposed to be by Major Rutherfurd, 1756
    - [113] Letter from Michael Kearney to James Alexander, 1756 May 4
    - [115] In order to defend..., 1756
    - [115] Plan of operations as proposed to Lord Loudoun by Major Walter Rutherfurd, Undated
    - [115] A plan of operation to chastise the Shawnees, support the Chickasaws, and to secure the friendship of the Catawbas and Cherokees, Undated
    - [117] Your is good..., Undated
    - [119] An anonymous contributor, Undated
    - [119] Extracts from the first plan of operations against Canada, sent by Messrs. Shirley and Warren to Governor Clinton, Undated
    - [119] An anonymous contributor replies to the remarks made for the non-repair of the fort at Saratoga, Undated
    - [121] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 31
    - [121] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 May 29
    - [123] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 June 8
    - [123] Copy of warrant from General William Shirley for John Erving, Jr., 1756 June 5
    - [125] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 June 17
    - [125] Letter from William Alexander, 1756 June 12
    - [127] Copy of warrant from General William Shirley to William Alexander, 1756 June 22
    - [129] Letter from General Abercrombie to Messrs. Livingston and Morris, 1756 July 5
    - [129] Letter from William Alexander, 1756 June 23
    - [129] Letter from William Alexander to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 June 21
    - [131] Letter from General William Shirley to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 August 28
    - [131] Letter from Lord Loudoun to P.V.B. Livingston, 1756 August 23
    - [133] Order and instructions from Major Walter Rutherfurd for 4th Battalion, 1756 September 9
    - [133] Letter from General William Shirley to P.V.B. Livingston, 1755 March
    - [135] Letter from William Alexander to Major Walter Rutherfurd, 1759 December 7
    - [135] Letter from General William Shirley to P.V.B. Livingston, 1757 January 8
    - [135] Letter from Major James Grant to Major Walter Rutherfurd, 1758 March 17
    - [137] Summons of Surrender to Fort Niagara by General Prideux, 1759 July 5
    - [137] The Bearer hereof..., 1759 July 9
    - [137] Humanity obliges me..., Undated
    - [139] Letter from General James Murray to Major Walter Rutherfurd, 1761 September 24
    - [141] Letter from James Stirling to John Duncan, 1762 October 25
    - [143] Letter from G. Christie to Walter Rutherfurd, 1750 October 9
    - [143] Letter from Walter Rutherfurd, 1756 February 20
    - [145] Letter from James Sterling to John Duncan, 1763 July 25
    - [145] Letter from James Sterling to John Duncan, 1763 August 7
    - [147] Rules and by-laws agreed upon by the proprietors settled on the tract lying between lakes Erie and Ontario, Undated
    - [149] Letter from Michael Ray to Walter Rutherfurd and others, 1766 June 14
    - [149] Letter from James Stirling to Messrs. Livingston, Rutherfurd, and Company, 1763 September 8
    - [151] Letter from Major Walter Rutherfurd to Gilbert Elliot, 1757 September 25
    - [151] Draft of a letter from Major John Rutherfurd to J. Scott, 1757 September 8
    - [151] Draft of letter from Major John Rutherfurd to Gilbert Elliot, 1757 November 28
    - [151] Draft of letter from Major John Rutherfurd to Gilbert Elliot, 1758 January 11
    - [153] Dear Donaldson..., Undated
    - [155] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 June 19
    - [155] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 June 26
    - [155] When the Head..., Undated
    - [156] Letter from Eliuh Spencer to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 July 21
    - [157] I am in..., Undated
    - [157] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 July 7
    - [157] Letter from Robert Blackeney to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 July 14
    - [157] Letter from Elihu Spencer to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 July 11
    - [157] Letter from Elihu Spencer to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 July 19
    - [157] Letter from Elihu Spencer to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 July 21
    - [159] Letter from Elihu Spencer to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 August 5
    - [159] Yesterday came to..., 1758 August 23
    - [159] We have no..., 1758 August 28
    - [159] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 August 12
    - [159] Your letter of 31..., 1758 August 15
    - [159] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 August 19
    - [159] Letter from Elihu Spencer to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 August
    - [159] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 August 20
    - [161] Letter from Elihu Spencer to P.V.B. Livingston, 1758 August 25
    - [161] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 June 1
    - [161] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 June 18
    - [161] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 June 22
    - [163] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 July 7
    - [163] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 July 17
    - [165] I am just now..., 1759 July 23
    - [165] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 July 27
    - [167] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 July 30
    - [169] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 August 6
    - [169] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 August 15
    - [171] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 August 22
    - [171] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 August 28
    - [173] Yours of the 23rd inst., 1759 September 1
    - [173] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 September 3
    - [173] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 September 7
    - [175] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 September 17
    - [175] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 September 27
    - [177] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 October 5
    - [177] I had yours by the last..., 1759 October 20
    - [179] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 November 26
    - [179] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1759 October 18
    - [181] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1760 September 6
    - [183] Letter from John Brainerd to P.V.B. Livingston, 1762 April 22
    - [185] Copy of the Letters patent made by the Duke of York, etc. in favor of Richard Nichols, 1664 April 2
    - [187] Petition from the proprietors of Nova Caesarea or New Jersey to the King's Most Excellent Majesty, Undated
    - [189] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1764 August 14
    - [189] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1764 July 15
    - [189] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1764 July 28
    - [191] Certificate of Lewis Morris, Governor of N.J., of the surrender by the Proprietaries to her Majesty Queen Anne, 1745 February 20
    - [193] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1764 November 7
    - [193] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1764 September 22
    - [195] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1765 May 13
    - [195] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1764 December 3
    - [195] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1765 March 23
    - [197] Yours by the Corporall, 1766 May 27
    - [197] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1765 June 10
    - [197] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1765 July 14
    - [197] Yours of the 24th May, 1765 June 18
    - [197] Letter from John Rutherfurd to Walter Rutherfurd, 1766
    - [199] Rough sketch and map of Fort Niagara, Undated
    - [203] Some statistical notes connected with New York from 1664 to 1800, Undated
    - [203] Letter from Robert Livingston to James Alexander, 1753 January 22
    - [205] Petition from the Isle of Barbados, Undated
  - Subseries I.E: Volume IV, 1697-1756
    TBD
    - [1] December 21, 1697 letter D. Gregory, 1697 December 21
    - [5] James Logan, 1718 July 17
    - [5] Dear Namsake, 1719 January 22
    - [7] James Logan, 1718 August 3
    - [9] James Logan, 1718 August 9
    - [9] James Logan, 1718 August 7
    - [11] I had the agreeable, 1733 April 9
    - [13] Letter from J. Johnson to Charles Dunster, 1706 February 19
    - [15] I had the honour of yours, Undated
    - [17] Lewis Morris, 1709 November 3
    - [17] Robert Morris, Undated
    - [19] To all whom these..., 1713
    - [21] Letter from J. Ormstun to James Alexander, 1715 May 12
    - [21] J. Ormstun, 1715 May 10
    - [23] Letter to James Alexander, Undated
    - [23] Letter to James Alexander, London, 1716 April
    - [25] Discoursing..., 1716 April 21
    - [27] Letter from James Alexander to Edward Richier, 1717 July 29
    - [29] Letter from James Logan to James Alexander, 1722 May 10
    - [29] James Logan, 1725 July 8
    - [31] We underwritten, 1727 September 7
    - [31] Copy I had the favour, 1729 August
    - [33] Letter from Governor William Cosby to R. VanDam, 1731 January 27
    - [35] Copie Being informed..., 1731 January 27
    - [37] Daniel Horsmandeu, 1734 February 11
    - [37] Governor William Cosby, 1732 February 23
    - [39] Copy of Paris's petition, 1735 November 17
    - [39] Copy complaint of Governor William Cosby, 1735 November 17
    - [41] Copy Report from the Lords of Trade, 1735 August 28
    - [43] Letter to Captain Lewis Morris, 1716 September 4
    - [43] Robert Morris I was the..., 1735 October 16
    - [45] Copy of a letter from James Alexander to Murray, 1744 December 19
    - [47] A Bill to prevent the issuing, Undated
    - [49] The inclose I wrote..., 1748 March 7
    - [51] Letter from Thomas Lee to James Alexander, 1748 July 5
    - [51] Letter from Robert Morris to James Alexander, 1747 June 3
    - [53] Thomas Lee, 1748 July 1
    - [55] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1732 May 3
    - [56] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1736 February 27
    - [57] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1736 October 28
    - [59] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1738 August 21
    - [59] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1738 July 18
    - [61] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1739 May 30
    - [61] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1739 March 11
    - [63] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1739 June 4
    - [65] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1740 September 5
    - [65] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1740 August 1
    - [67] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1740 December 15
    - [67] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1740 November 12
    - [69] Receipt, 1743 January 20
    - [69] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1743 March 2
    - [69] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1742 February 14
    - [71] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1742 July 3
    - [71] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1742 March 10
    - [73] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1742 September 3
    - [73] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1742 July 10
    - [75] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1734 March 11
    - [75] William Alexander, 1765 March 9
    - [75] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1742 September 8
    - [77] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1747 April 7
    - [77] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1747 April
    - [79] Copy of a letter from James Alexander to Peter Collinson, 1747 July 20
    - [81] Letter from Cadwallader Colden to James Alexander, 1757 June 3
    - [81] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1747 October 14
    - [83] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1754 September 19
    - [85] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1756 March 25
    - [87] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1756 April 1
    - [89] Peter Collinson, 1756 May 9
    - [91] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1756 August 12
    - [93] Letter from Peter Collinson to James Alexander, 1756 August 12
  - Subseries I.F: Volume V, 1783-1801
    - [1] Letter to John Rutherfurd, 1783 February 9
    - [1] Letter to Miss Livingston, 1783 March 7
    - [2] With pleasure I now..., 1798 July 2
    - [2] We hope this will find..., 1798 June 22
    - [2] We have been very happy..., 1783 August 4
    - [2] I take the liberty..., 1783 September 12
    - [3] Daily and yourly..., 1798 August 7
    - [3] Mr. R says..., 1798 July 28
    - [3] I enclose your letter..., 1783 September 12
    - [3] Mr. Deas and Mr. Pinkner, 1783 September 27
    - [4] We are arrived what..., 1783 November 6
    - [4] I received your short..., 1783 November 13
    - [4] I closed my letter..., 1783 November 15
    - [4] I am sorry Miss Johnson..., 1784 May 29
    - [4] We were yesterday..., 1798 August 22
    - [5] Such strange report..., 1798 August 30
    - [5] The Dye is cast..., 1798 September 3
    - [5] Our cause came on..., 1784 June 20
    - [5] Since I last wrote..., 1784 June 22
    - [6] We arrived here..., 1798 November 4
    - [6] We have received your..., 1784 July 6
    - [6] I have been looking..., 1784 July 26
    - [7] The letter I design'd..., 1798 November 9
    - [7] We have not heard..., 1799 January 4
    - [7] I forgot to leave an..., 1784 September 30
    - [7] I received yours of 5th..., 1784 September 30
    - [8] Yours, long look..., 1799 January 14
    - [8] Nothing has lately..., 1799 January 26
    - [8] I am here on Logan's..., 1784 November 30
    - [8] To morrow..., 1784 October 29
    - [8] Having an Opportunity..., 1785 September 28
    - [9] We are glad to hear..., 1799 February 7
    - [9] Mr. Taylor has now..., 1799 February 15
    - [9] As I am constantly..., 1785 December 18
    - [9] This encloses..., 1785 November 16
    - [10] When I before..., 1799 February 24
    - [10] With pleasure we..., 1799 March 8
    - [10] As our Neighbour..., 1786 August 12
    - [10] We made a very good..., 1786 May 24
    - [11] We had yesterday..., 1796 March 24
    - [11] ...wrote to Mr. Stevens, 1786 September 11
    - [11] As James Spoul..., 1787 March 7
    - [11] Have delayed..., 1799 March 22
    - [12] We received your welcome..., 1799 April 6
    - [12] We have seen the Vicount..., 1799 April 9
    - [12] We arrived here at two..., 1786 July
    - [12] We were much..., 1787 July 22
    - [13] Our colds and..., 1797 April 18
    - [13] Tho we wrote..., 1799 April 22
    - [13] We have long expected..., 1787 June 1
    - [13] Pero arrived this day..., 1787 July 25
    - [13] Pero arrived this day..., 1787 July 25
    - [14] I forgot to mention..., 1787 August 9
    - [14] You will please..., 1787 September 11
    - [15] We received yours..., 1799 May 3
    - [15] Hoping you parted..., 1799 May 30
    - [15] We got to town..., 1787 December 18
    - [15] Jacob Depue..., 1787 December 23
    - [16] We duly received..., 1799 June 16
    - [16] We were in hopes you..., 1787 August 31
    - [16] Not having any..., 1788 January 8
    - [17] We congradulate you..., 1799 July 12
    - [17] It is long since..., 1788 February 20
    - [17] I enclose..., 1788 March 19
    - [18] We were glad to hear..., 1799 August 19
    - [18] We received yours..., 1799 July 23
    - [18] James Sprewlhal, 1788 March 29
    - [19] The Dye is cast and..., 1799 August 26
    - [19] I might have wrote..., 1799 November 3
    - [19] We were happy to hear..., 1789 January 12
    - [19] I came home late..., 1789 June 5
    - [20] We quite long..., 1799 December 3
    - [20] We were glad to find..., 1799 November 19
    - [20] Parker called..., 1789 July 4
    - [20] Mr. Stevens..., 1789 November 8
    - [20] I remained two days..., 1789 October 30
    - [21] We were happy at last..., 1799 December 13
    - [21] We received your..., 1800 January 21
    - [21] Mr. Stevens has just..., 1789 November 18
    - [21] If you leave now..., 1789 November 21
    - [22] We were much disappointed..., 1800 February 26
    - [22] I expect this will..., 1800 March 22
    - [22] We have just heard..., 1789 December 19
    - [22] We got to town..., 1789 November 29
    - [23] Receive here with..., 1800 April 6
    - [23] We are quite impatient..., 1800 April 14
    - [23] Mr. Willen gives us..., 1790 January 9
    - [24] Never have we seen..., 1800 April 21
    - [24] We were glad to hear..., 1800 May 12
    - [24] We quite long to see..., 1790 August 4
    - [24] Received yours by..., 1790 February 13
    - [24] Mr. Lawrence called..., 1790 March 3
    - [24] We send a copy..., 1815 February 18
    - [25] On Saturday..., 1800 June 23
    - [25] We were glad to hear you..., Undated
    - [25] We were much entertained..., 1790 November 21
    - [25] We expect this will..., 1790 October 25
    - [26] You'll see by the..., 1800 July 21
    - [26] Some hot weather..., 1800 June 30
    - [26] I am glad to have..., 1790 December 5
    - [26] David is just..., 1790 December 12
    - [27] ...me to write again, 1800 July 22
    - [27] We expected you..., 1800 July 25
    - [27] Once moved take..., 1791 February 12
    - [27] Most impatiently..., 1791 January 22
    - [28] We were much pleased..., 1800 August 1
    - [28] Having the opportunity..., 1800 August 5
    - [28] I am just returned..., 1791 September 30
    - [28] Sunday morning; We had heard..., Undated
    - [29] Yours of 20 first..., 1800 August 20
    - [29] The illustrious..., 1791 November 5
    - [29] I enclose as..., 1791 October 30
    - [30] On Saturday..., 1800 August 25
    - [30] We had the pleasure..., 1800 September 2
    - [30] While at Leisure..., 1791 November 20
    - [30] As we intended..., 1791 November 25
    - [31] The Die is cast..., 1800 September 6
    - [31] I have just received..., 1800 September 9
    - [31] Two days ago..., 1791 December 1
    - [31] I received yours..., 1791 December 6
    - [32] I did not expect..., 1800 December 23
    - [32] We received yours this..., 1800 November 12
    - [32] We were very happy..., 1792 January 6
    - [32] Breakhouse has..., Undated
    - [33] We have long wish'd, 1801 January 9
    - [33] I was much pleased..., 1802 January 25
    - [33] I am to acknowledge..., 1792 February 5
    - [33] We received yours by..., 1792 January 30
    - [34] I am sorry to have..., 1801 February 6
    - [34] I have two Letters..., 1801 January 26
    - [34] I am happy to have..., 1792 February 8
    - [34] I have not receive..., Undated
    - [35] We have received yours..., 1801 February 11
    - [35] I am happy to acquaint..., 1801 February 13
    - [35] The Marys and children..., 1792 March 4
    - [35] Since I wrote you..., 1792 March 10
    - [36] The there is no great..., 1801 February 19
    - [36] We received yours this..., 1801 June 30
    - [36] We are to be abroad..., 1792 March 14
    - [36] Yours is just arrived..., 1792 March 28
    - [37] We were all very happy..., 1801 August 30
    - [37] We were happy to hear..., 1801 September 29
    - [37] We congratulate you both..., 1792 May 20
    - [37] May 5 Pero arrived before Dinner..., Undated
    - [38] Since we wrote by..., 1801 October 17
    - [38] In continuation..., 1801 October 25
    - [38] We quite long to see..., 1792 July 27
    - [38] We long to hear what..., 1792 September 1
    - [39] At Genl Gates' dined, 1801 November 1
    - [39] I am almost wore at..., 1802 January 28
    - [39] I was prevented writing..., 1792 November 26
    - [39] Since last have received..., 1792 September 9
    - [40] Robert and I..., 1802 April 22
    - [40] The Mary R. is writing..., 1803 May 23
    - [40] Tho' we heard some..., 1792 December 30
    - [40] Expecting this will find..., Undated
    - [41] I received yours on..., 1803 June 6
    - [41] We were happy yesterday..., 1798 January 4
    - [42] We received your of..., 1798 January 16
    - [42] As Mary C. carries..., 1798 January 27
    - [43] Feb 10 We are sorry to find..., Undated
    - [43] Jan 30; Recd yours of Sunday, Undated
    - [44] We have received..., 1793 February 21
    - [44] We were much pleased..., 1798 March 20
    - [44] Feb 12; A deep snow..., Undated
    - [45] I wrote to you on..., 1793 March 21
    - [45] Mar 24; We were quite impatient..., Undated
    - [46] We are just come from..., 1792 March 25
    - [46] ...have received from, 1793 May 15
    - [47] We received yours with..., 1793 July 2
    - [47] ...received yours, 1793 May 27
    - [48] We were glad to see..., 1793 July 31
    - [48] I have the pleasure..., 1793 October 8
    - [49] We are much disappointed..., 1793 November 18
    - [49] Sunday Eve; Your M. has got a..., Undated
  - Subseries I.G: Volume VI, 1792-1803
    - [50] I hope you would..., 1793 December 1
    - [50] Read yours of last week..., 1793 December 9
    - [51] This afternoon Mr..., 1793 December 9
    - [51] At last we received..., 1793 December 15
    - [52] We received yours..., 1793 December 18
    - [52] Rec'd your note..., 1793 December 25
    - [53] I have received your..., 1793 December 31
    - [53] Dec 26; At length, Undated
    - [54] Tho some of us..., 1794 January 6
    - [54] William Morris, 1794 January 30
    - [55] William Morris's return, 1794 February 11
    - [55] Tuesday 9th; A fine day..., Undated
    - [56] We congratulate you..., 1794 March 8
    - [57] I have just wrote..., 1794 March 12
    - [57] I sent Misseuer..., 1794 March 12
    - [58] I am sorry to inform..., 1794 March 13
    - [58] I expect this may..., 1794 March 17
    - [59] I have made the grand..., 1794 April 16
    - [59] ...near four weeks, 1794 April 26
    - [60] I have received several..., 1794 May 5
    - [60] This serves as a cover..., Undated
    - [60] Weds Ever; Expecting this Day..., Undated
    - [61] Yesterday sent off..., 1794 May 10
    - [61] We are quite impatient..., 1794 May 24